this is by far the best funnel if you
are a coach course creador and want to
get more clients more people buying from
you a low ticket offer that can make you
Millions I've been working with my
clients to use this exact funnel this is
what we're using in our business and I
actually went through and funnel hacked
about 45 different funnels and I found
that the best ones are using this exact
structure so I'm going to break it down
for you nobody's really teaching this
some have called it a by different names
I'm borrowing from different strategies
and we're going to bring them all
together for you in this video for those
of you that I have not met yet my name
is Jeremiah Kowski and I have been in
the coaching training and online
marketing space for over 21 years I
built multiple businesses over $10
million a year and I spend every single
day in the trenches with my clients
scaling their businesses and helping
them make tens of thousands of dollars
in the beginning all the way up to tens
of millions of dollars as they grow okay
so I'm going to break down for you is
this is how this funnel works and it's
based around the idea of getting people
to trust you before you ask them to buy
something from you and we use a
combination of low
ticket semi self liquidating offers
which some people call it self
liquidating offers some people call it
the Miffy low ticket is actually how I
like to build trust with people more
than anything else but we also include
on the back end of it a high
ticket for those who are most qualified
who they have to join the low ticket
first before they ever even hear about
the high ticket offer and what I find is
is that this this is one of the most
ethical ways to do this it feels really
good you're not salesy at all if you
watch any of my videos if you watch How
I market sell and teach people I'm not
salesy at all and yet it brings in tons
of cash when you do this the right way
so I'm going to break down for you what
this is and how this works okay so what
you have to do in any kind of offer
strategy that you're
running is you want to make sure that
you can get in front of the right people
at the right time with the right message
okay and so what that means is that
always breaks down to some kind of a
video which is between 12 to 30 minutes
long okay and I'm not including videos
such as social media videos Instagram
reals or YouTube videos these are
more they fall in the advertising or
traffic generation Lane to where they
come before this type of a thing for
somebody to get access to this video
they have to give you their email
address and what you're going to promise
in this video is a very
big
bold promise like we're going to teach
you our strategy to make millions with
one simple funnel that's going to work
for you as far as that goes and then you
have able to sign up for this I'm going
to show you how to start your own online
course business that generates six
figures or here's another one I'm going
to show you how to have the kind of
energy and Authority that allows you to
close more High ticket clients the way
that's been working for our clients and
what it is is you teach this in a
between a 12 to 30
minute micro video class okay so a lot
of people they call this by different
names they call it either a vssl a video
sales letter I don't like calling into V
A vssl personally cuz it's not really a
traditional vssl okay so we're not going
the traditional vssl route it actually
is a training and that's the key and it
uses a model that I like to call the
reverse training model Okay the reason
why it's called the reverse training
model is it's the opposite of literally
what everybody else has been doing for
the last 10 years when it comes to
webinars or online training and at the
end of this video I'm actually going to
break down for you how the reverse model
works okay how the reverse training
model works the structure of it as far
as that goes but I'm going to break down
the funnel for you right here so this 12
to 30 minute video they have to give you
their email address for to sign up for
that so how are you sending people to
this you can either have YouTube videos
like this you can tell people to go
click a link to go download a video
training as far as that goes you could
have it on your Instagram reals people
leave a comment and then it sends them a
DM or you could run Facebook or in
Instagram ads and then the advertising
campaigns send them to sign up for this
video training now again it's a it's
going to be a big bold promise and
here's the part that I think a lot of
people Miss there's no way that you're
going to be able to deliver at scale
what that big bold promise is in about
12 minutes but what you can
do because you don't want to over te you
don't want to give a bunch of
information information is worthless in
this in this equation what you want to
do is use it to build trust to people to
show them your system your strategies to
show them enough information that they
want what you have that's next and what
do you have that's next and these are
the two parts of it that really make
this funnel work so well especially if
you're running paid
advertising you have two parts to this
offer okay
so what we're going to have is we're
going to
have the 12 to 20 minute video right
here and the two parts to the offer is a
$1
upsell now the $1 upell gives people a
course and this is a mini course it's
longer than a 12 to 20 minute or 30
minute let's put 30 minutes right there
because really could be 12 to 30 minutes
I've seen any number of different
lengths of that but the $1 course has a
perceived value of about $400 to
,000 you could put a price tag on it of
that and it's about 30 to 90 minutes in
length you could also do it in multiple
sessions you could do three 30 minute
sessions but it has enough value and
information that people really feel
served as far as that goes and it solves
one really big problem that you're
presenting to this person right here
over here okay so you're going to
encourage them give them an overview of
what you cover both in that $1 offer but
here's the other part you also give them
the opportunity to get a
trial of your main program
okay and so your main program especially
if you do a payment plan could run
anywhere from 97 to
$297 a month on a membership and you
give people access to that by watching
this video you tell them very lightly
about there being a trial to this
program your goal is actually to get
them to get the
$1 course because in that course you're
also going to tell them about the trial
so you're going to you're going to
lightly touch on the trial in this the
goal of this video is not necessarily to
drive people to the trial but you're
going to let them know that it exists
okay soft sell it but what you're going
to do is you're going to really try to
get people to buy into whatever this $1
thing is and here's why this works so
well for ads with Facebook ads because
you can optimize the algorithm really
really
well for a $1 low commitment sale to
bring in the most qualified people for
you and so the goal is again this is
also then going to sell them on whatever
that trial is we run our ads with a
purchase goal instead of a lead goal now
because we're able to bring in
more paid people now here's the thing it
might cost you $10 to
$30 per $1 sale that you get and that's
normal but those are hyper qualified
people according to the algorithm and
the chances are you're going to be able
to
convert one in every three to four of
those people to whatever your membership
is especially if it's a trial offer and
here's the other thing included with the
trial you can give people free
courses
as bonuses okay so these are bonus
courses that they get to keep forever
just for trying it out and I like
anywhere from a 7 to a 14-day trial
period I've also seen it you could do a
uh a a a 30-day money back guarantee
trial where they have to pay but it's a
money back guarantee these all work
different strategies just depends on how
many people you want to push through the
door there's a little more customer
service involved if you're doing a free
trial but either way you can push a lot
of people through the door and if you
have a really great
program it it'll speak for itself as far
as that goes so they get to keep the
free courses just for trying it out so
now you're incentivizing the trial
massively as far as that goes and you're
qualifying who's going to try it out by
having your ads Target people that are
going to grab the $1 upsell okay so this
$1 upsell is a bit of a Trojan
course as far as that goes you call it a
course you give it value that's worth
maybe $500 to
$1,000 but really what it is it's about
30 60 90 minutes of you providing some
value and you're going deeper than what
you did in this initial video so again
the funnel goes like
this you
have a landing page they sign up for
with their email address to get
something really valuable something big
something awesome that you're going to
teach them in a free training and here's
the other cool thing you could literally
say this training is normally $97 but
for right now it's
free so you make people really excited
that there's value in this and then you
send them to go watch whatever that 12
to 30 minute training video
is and then in that you make them an
opportunity to grab the $1
course low commitment right cuz here's
the thing your
trial has a bit of a commitment on top
of it you're giving them a course for
free but they're going to be jumping
into a community with you they're going
to they're they're going to be put into
a membership that's going to charge them
a couple hundred dollar a month if they
stay in and they'll they might feel
embarrassed for cancelling so you give
people one of two options
here and either of them works fine with
you the $1 course which then Loops them
right back to the trial because it's a
course right here or you get them to go
over to that trial offer and so this
funnel right here you can make this
Evergreen and here's the way that I plan
on doing it in my business is I'm
actually going to create three to four
of these on different topics I might
make a topic on creating a course I
might make one
on running your app
another one on creating your lead magnet
another one on you know how to how to
host a zoom call as far as or how to how
to create a webinar or or how to do a
video salesletter or something like or
or even just how to make one of these
videos like this kind of a great idea
and so whatever that is that's going to
be my hook that I'm going to put here
for their email address now here's the
part I haven't even talked
about because you're capturing their
email address for this even if they
don't grab the upsell you can have some
autoresponders for that even if they
don't grab the
trial you can then throw
in what I
call the ultimate trust building
exercise not only are you going to have
content on your
Instagram you might even have it on your
YouTube like we have right here and you
can email people with pieces of content
because they're already on your email
list and then that builds trust Loops
them right back into the system but you
can also send them to either a
live or
pre-recorded
Evergreen
webinar because they're already on your
email list because they've already
watched a video with you because most of
them because you're targeting qualified
people with a $1
upsell and a trial and you have the
algorithm finding those people they are
ready and itching for more of what you
have to offer you're going to send
qualified people to something that's
between about
60 maybe 90 to 120 Minutes of a training
that's going to be a longer form
training and at the end of it you're
going to pitch them again on the trial
as far as that
goes and this process right here allows
you to start with low commitment
12-minute video video 20-minute video $1
course this is great allows the
algorithm to show your ad to people that
are more qualified because they have to
put something up front to access that
just a little bit but it's enough to get
the algorithm to show it to better
people and then if they don't buy from
there great spend some time with us for
an hour 90 minutes 120 minutes and you
can either do it live or personally I'm
I would do it
pre-recorded and you can have them
access a longer form training where
again you're going to Loop it right back
to them being able to join you in the
trial period
okay and so this funnel right
here will get you tons of qualified
people into your membership programs and
again your trial could
be low C like pay $60 for your first
month pay 27 bucks for your first month
30-day money back guarantee but the idea
is if you can attach to it some kind of
a risk
reversal
and what Dan Kennedy and Russell Brunson
called the mithy most incredible free
gift ever you throw in a mythy on top of
this that gives them some extra free
courses that you have I like to give
people my course on funnel building my
course on Facebook ads and these are
these are high quality courses that I
give them completely free just for
trying it out so you're not only you're
doing risk reversal with either a
moneyback or a trial and you're giving
them free
courses by the time they get here they
are so Ultra qualified and itching to
jump in that the chances of them saying
no at that point are so
low that you have a system that is an
evergreen sales system that you can step
away from the reason why I I designed it
this way and I found people that are
doing this is because if you are doing
Live Events after live event after live
event like I was doing for months and
months and months to get people onto
your email list hosting live webinars
trying to run challenges to do this two
things have happened number one you are
working way too hard in your business I
think and number two people's attention
span right now thanks to artificial
intelligence tick Tok Instagram reals
and
YouTube thanks to all those things
people's attention span is so much lower
than it was years
ago and so what this does is it allows
you to tap into the instant
gratification that people crave and
desire and being able to get something
without a lot of commitment but if you
have something that's really incredible
to offer these people the stick rate is
extremely high and the reason why we
have it this way is because it's
designed to qualify the right people at
the right time in front of you if you
know you're messaging which we coach
people on in my coaching program the
accelerator program if you know how to
create ads that work we show you how to
do that in my accelerator program you
can get people to join you with very
little
effort with very few hours invested on
your part to join your programs now I
told you by the end of this I was going
to give you what that reverse training
system is so the reverse training system
is this and I found this because I went
through a number of different people's
funnels as as how as as how they're
doing it and I noticed that all the
people in the last 6 months have been
using this system and then I found a guy
he actually started calling it something
like I forget what his name was but he
didn't call it this but he called it it
was like a trauma informed webinar is
what he and I was like wa that's
actually really cool so here's he
said is that in that 12 to 20 minute 30
minute
video and I even tested this about a
month and a half ago in one of my
webinars I did a two-hour webinar we had
the best sales that we've ever had by
doing this in this process the reverse
training process so a
traditional
webinar traditional
training follows where you give an
introduction who you are what your track
record is and then you go into the
training and then you give a big sales
pitch at the end so the reverse training
goes this way it's literally the reverse
order you start the training your
12-minute training whatever that is
with your offer you literally tell
people what you have to offer at the
beginning stage one and and you don't
hard sell it but you let them know
listen we've been making money with this
this is what we offer this is what we
help people with if you get some value
from this we'd love to have you join us
so now you ripped the Band-Aid off of
them worrying that you're going to sell
them by the end of it and here's the
reason why this works because people are
so sick and tired of being pitched to on
free trainings online and so now if you
make them the offer at the
beginning you've literally flipped the
script and now their guard is down
because they're like oh well he already
did that so now I want to sit and lean
forward and listen to what they have to
say it's incredible so now number two
you go into the implementation
this is going to be the value that
you're going to deliver but you don't
want to over te on this part and that's
a little bit of a key Nuance that I
teach my clients in my accelerator
program as well is how to not over te
but figure out how to get just up to the
point of people's understanding
comprehension and retention okay of
what's going to show them what they want
to know this video right here is
actually a great example of how I I
would do that I've taught just enough in
this video but I've not Tak Tak like
hours to break down every little Nuance
of it I'm sure you want to learn those
things I teach those things in my
accelerator program however I'm not over
teaching in this video but I am giving
you the right amount of value for the
for the conversation and that's exactly
what you do in the middle part of that
and then you actually end
it with an emotional
story and this is the crazy part about
it because people buy based on emotion
so most traditional webinars they go
emotional story testimonials case
studies all this stuff at the beginning
and then implementation and then a sales
pitch the reverse format is you actually
talk about what you have to sell in the
beginning you get it right out of the
way you know and then you go into what
that implementation is you you you give
that value that you're going to deliver
that promised value and then you give
stories you can share case studies you
can share your story how you got started
how you found this the process of how
you found this what you've done your
process and how you've helped people as
far as that goes and so then the reverse
format of this creates a different
trigger in people's minds where they are
excited by the end of it and it excites
something inside of them deeply that is
like this is different than anything
else that I've ever seen I wasn't sold
to and I feel really really good about
this person that I just listened to and
you're connecting with them emotionally
at the end of it which ding ding ding is
the buying
trigger that gets people to buy into the
thing that you're selling okay they
already know what you have to sell you
don't have to oversell it you're going
to teach them but not over te and then
you're going to tap into that emotional
driver that heart piece that gets people
to take action and then with this
whatever your call to action is you'll
touch on the call to action again at the
end you do want a call to action to be
the last thing that you mentioned but
you're just going to B basically recap
what you had talked about in the
beginning you're going to touch on it
once more tell people how to find it
what the limited time offer is whatever
that is whatever their next steps are
with you after you've gone into the
emotional side of it so now you've
already gone you you've touched the
logical side you've already told them
what you have to offer but now you're
looping it back to
emotion and then bringing them right to
whatever that offer is and so now
they're going to leave that feeling
really good and excited and the next
time they see from you they're going to
remember that feeling that you ended it
on a high
note and then they're going to want to
either join whatever it is that you have
and they're in your system or if they
haven't bought from you they didn't take
the trial they didn't take the
mythy when you email them later they're
going to remember that and they're going
to register for the pre-recorded webinar
or whatever your next training is or
maybe take you up next week on the offer
sometimes it takes people a little bit
of time to make a decision to do that
but when you follow this format and you
do what I showed you in this video it
works and it works really well and I
think it'll work for you as well okay
listen I'd love to work with you inside
of my accelerator program right now we
have a waiting list for it you can go
check that out over my website go get
your name on the waiting list I'd love
to help you build your business the
right way we'll talk soon have a good
one